Stephen Jay Gould Papers, 1899-2004
Stanford University Libraries.
- Series 1. Correspondence
  - Subseries 4. Incoming letters, 1985-1989
    - Gl - Go (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Gr - Gw (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Ha (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - He (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Hi - Hy (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - K & S Speakers (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Kang, Won-Yong (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Kelly, Allan O. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Kinnel, R. B. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Kwok, John (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Ka (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Ke - Kj (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Kl - Ky (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Leake, B. E. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Lewis, Susan W. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Lincoln, Tim (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - La (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Le (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Li - Ly (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - McElroy, Michael B. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Montagu, Ashley (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Morohishi, Kazuo (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Ma (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Ma (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Mc - Me (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Mi - Mo (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Mu - My (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Subseries 5. Incoming letters, 1963-1974
    - Abbott, R. Tucker (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Addicott, Warren O. (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Aleu, M. Olga (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Alexander, R. McNeill (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Allen, Garland E. (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Ab - Ay (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Beers, John R. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Bock, Walter (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Bretsky, Peter W. and Sara S. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Ba - Be (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Bi - By (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Chappell, John E., Jr. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Chastain, Murray (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Clark, George R., II (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Cock, Alan (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Cohen, Ralph (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Cracraft, Joel (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Crompton, A. W. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Ca - Cl (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Co - Cu (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Dodson, Peter (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Dunlop, John T. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Da - Du (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Eldredge, Niles (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Emmott, Margaret (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Ea - Ey (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Fox, H. Munro (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Freeman, William H. (Freeman, Cooper & Co.) (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Fa - Fr (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Goss, Richard J. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Gould, Leonard and Eleanor (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Greiner, Gary O. G. and Betty (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Greene, John C. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Ga - Gu (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Hallam, Anthony (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Halsell, Grace (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Hyami, Haru (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Ha - Hu (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Imbrie, John (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - I (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Jefferies, R. P. S. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Jerrison, Harry J. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Ralph G. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Johnston, Richard F. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Ja - Jo (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - J Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Kaesler, Roger L. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Kidwell, James F. (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Kier, Porter M. (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Kokshaysky, N. V. (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Ka - Ku (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Lewis, Harlan (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Livingston, Katherine (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - La - Ly (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Mackenzie, Fred T. (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Macurda, Donald B., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Merriam, Daniel F. (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Ma - Mc (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Me - My (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, Clifford M. (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Gareth J. (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Nevo, Eviatar (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Newell, Norman D. (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Newton, John (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Na - Ny (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Oliver, William A., Jr. (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Ostrom, John H. (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Oa - Ox (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Peisch, Mark L. (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Piip, Leida (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Pa - Pr (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Q (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Radinsky, Len (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Raup, David M. (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Ray, D. Michael (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Reese, David S. (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Reyment, Richard (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Rolfe, W. D. I. (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Rowell, A. J. (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Rudwick, Martin J. S. (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Ra - Ru (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Schopf, Thomas J. M. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Sepkoski, Jack (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Simpson, George Gaylord (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Solbrig, Otto T. (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Sokal, Robert R. (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Stanley, Steven M. (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Stebbins, G. Ledyard (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Sa - Sl (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Sm - Sz (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Thayer, Charles W. (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Thomas, Roger D. K. (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Thompson, Ida (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Torrens, Hugh (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Ta - Ty (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - U (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Van Valen, Leigh (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Vermeij, Geerat J. (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Va - Vo (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Wa - Wy (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Y (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Zinn, Donald J. (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Z (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - X, Y, Z Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 6. Incoming letters, 1989-1993
    - Ob - Ox (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - O Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Perry, Leslie G. (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Pa - Pe (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Pi - Pu (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Q (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Rockman, Alexis (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Rogovin, Milton (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Ro - Ry (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Ra - Ri (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Schierenberg, Dieter (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Sibley, Charles (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Suchard, Marc A. (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Sykes, Christopher (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Sa (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Sc - Se (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Sh - Sl (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Sm - Sq (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - St - Sw (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Ta - Ty (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - T Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Va - Vu (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - V Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Wa (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - We - Wi (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Wo - Wu (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Z (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 7. Incoming letters, 1990-1997
    - Anderson, Wyatt W. (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Aa - Ae (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Ag - Al (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Am - Ap (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Ar (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - As - Au (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Baker, Robert J. (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Belton, Neil (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Bintliff, John (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Blake, Carl David (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Block, Laurie (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Boss, Kenneth J. (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Breguet, Georges (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Brockman, John (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Peter G. (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Broxon, Duane (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Bryant, Ruth A. (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Bunge, William (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Burgess, Kathryn H. (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Burns, Joan Simpson (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Burns, Ken (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Butler, Syd (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Ba (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Be (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Be (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Bi - Bj (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Bl (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Bo (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Br (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Br (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Bu (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Bu (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Cohen, Claudine (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Corman, Cid (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Courtright, Frederick T. (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Ca (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Ce - Cha (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Che - Ci (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Cl (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Co (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Cr - Cz (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Darby, Grace (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Debus, Allen A. (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Dennett, Daniel C. (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Dershowitz, Alan M. (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Dover, Gabriel A. (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Da (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Da (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - De (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Di - Dj (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Do (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Dr - Dy (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Elder, David (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Ea - Ed (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Eg - Ek (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - El - En (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Er - Ey (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Fabian, Andy (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Fazio, Russ (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Fellows, John (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Ferguson, Evan R. (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Fern, Alan (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Foote, Mike (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Freedle, Roy (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Fa (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Fe (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Fi (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Fl (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Fo (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Fu (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Fra (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Fre - Fry (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Gee, Henry (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Golden, William T. (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr. (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Gould, Stephen Jay (To Agnes Pilot) (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Guerrero, Ricardo (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Ga (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Ge - Gh (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Gi - Gl (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Go (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Go (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Gr (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Gu - Gw (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Hannibal, Joseph (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Harlowe, Joan (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Horowitz, Paul (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Houff, S. A. (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Hab - Hal (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Ham - Han (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Har (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Has - Hay (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Hea - Hen (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Her - Hey (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Hi (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Hoa - Hol (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Hom - How (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Hu - Hy (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - I (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Ja (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Je (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Jo - Ju (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Katz, Bob (K & S Speakers) (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Kuralt, Charles (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Kutscheid, Timothy (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Ka (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Ke (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Kh - Ki (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Kj - Kn (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Ko - Kr (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Ku - Ky (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Paula Y. (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Levy-Leblond, Jean-Marc (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Lewis, Susan W. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - La (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Le (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Le (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Li (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Ll - Ly (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Machol, Robert E. (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - McCullough, David (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - McShea, Dan (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Milner, Richard (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Mirchandani, Ravi (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Milton, Jeffry B. (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Montagu, Ashley (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Mac - Mad (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Mag - Mar (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Mas - Maz (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Mc (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Me (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Mi (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Mo (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Mu - My (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Nevraumont, Peter N. (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Newell, Norman D. (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Nolen, Susan B. (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Na (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Ne (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Ni - Ny (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - O (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Piel, Jonathan (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Press, Michelle (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Pa (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Pe (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Pf - Pl (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Po - Pu (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - P Miscellaneous (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Q (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Rogovin, Milton and Anne (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Ra (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Re (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Rh - Ri (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Ro (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Ru - Ry (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - R Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Sagan, Carl (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Schierenberg, Dieter (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Scott, Eugenie C. (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Searchinger, Gene (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Sepkoski, J. John, Jr. (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Serageldin, Ismail (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Shearer, Rhonda Roland (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Shermer, Michael (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ellen (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Smith, John Maynard (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Squire, Larry R. (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Stillman, Lisa (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Sykes, Christopher (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Sa (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Sc (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Se (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Sh (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Si (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Sj (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Sk - Sl (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Sm (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Sn - Sp (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - St (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Sy - Sz (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - S Miscellaneous (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Ta - Te (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Th - To (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Tr - Ty (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - U - V (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Waldren, Mary-Anne (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Ted (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Wolschke-Bulmahn, Joachim (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Wa (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - We (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Wh (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Wi (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Wi (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Wo - Wy (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - W Miscellaneous (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Y - Z (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 8. Incoming letters, 1986-1992
    - Abrams, Susan E. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Adams, Robert McC. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Adams, Thomas B. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Ager, Derek (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Alberch, Pere (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Allmon, Warren D. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Amundson, Ron (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Ab - Ad (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Ag - Ai (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Ak - Al (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Am (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - An - Ap (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Ar (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - As - At (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Au - Az (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - A Miscellaneous (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Banks, Leslie (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Barber, Edwin (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Barrett, John (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Bell, Michael A. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Belton, Neil (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Bengtson, Stefan (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Bjarkman, Peter C. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Blanc, Marcel (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Block, Laurie (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Bok, Derek (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Boyer, Howard (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Bridie, Susan (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Brockman, John (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Ba (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Ba (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Ba (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Ba (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Be (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Be (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Bi - Bj (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Bl (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Bo (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Bo (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Br (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Br (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Bu (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Bu - By (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - B Miscellaneous (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Cab - Cal (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Cam (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Cap (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Car (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Cas - Cav (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Ce - Ch (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Cl (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Co (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Co (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Cr (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Cu - Cz (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - C Miscellaneous (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Dayan, Tamar (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - de Camp, L. Sprague (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Dershowitz, Alan M. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - de Souza, Anthony R. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Diamond, Jared M. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Donghi, Pino (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Dorit, Rob (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Dover, Gabriel A. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Durham, William H. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Da (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - De (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Di - Dj (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Do (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Dr (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Du - Dy (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - D Miscellaneous (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Eccles, Sir John (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Ehrlich, Paul R. (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Eisenberg, Leon (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Elder, David (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Eldredge, Niles (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Emerson, William K. (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Endler, John A. (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Erwin, Douglas H. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Evans, Barry (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Ea - Ec (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Ed - Eh (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Ei - El (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Em - En (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Ep - Es (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Et - Ey (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - E Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Fazio, Russ (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Fellows, John (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Fern, Alan (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Fischer, Anne Poindexter (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Fisher, Daniel C. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Flanagan, Vincent F. (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Foote, Mike (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Fa (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Fe (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Fi (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Fl - Fo (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Fr (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Fr (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Fu (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - F Miscellaneous (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Gale, Bob (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Galloway, James N. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Gardner, Martin (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Gates, Henry Louis, Jr. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Gazzaniga, Michael S. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Gilinsky, Norman L. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Glen, William (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Glennon, Lorraine (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Gordon, D. C. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Gore, Albert, Jr. (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Gould, Jay M. (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Ga (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Ge - Gh (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Gi (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Gl - Go (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Go (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Gr (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Gr (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Gr (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Gu - Gw (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - G Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Hall, Alvin L. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Hallam, Anthony (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Halpine, Susana M. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Harnad, Stevan (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Hill, H. Stanton (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Hoffenberg, Sir Raymond (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Ha (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Ha (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Ha (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Ha (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - He (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - He (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Hi (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Ho (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Ho (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Ho (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Ho (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Hu (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Hu - Hy (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - H Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Ia - In (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Is - Iz (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, J. G. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Ja (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Ja - Je (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Jo (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Jo (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Jo - Ju (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - I - J Miscellaneous (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Kamer, Nellie (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Katz, Bob (K & S Speakers) (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Kayzer, Wim (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Kea, Charlotte G. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Kelly, Allan O. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Kimura, Motoo (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Krimmel, Thomas (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Kruger, Michael (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Kurtz, Paul (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Ka (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Ka (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Ka (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Ke (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Ke - Kj (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Ki (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Kl (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Kn (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Ko (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Ko (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Kr (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Ku - Kw (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - K Miscellaneous (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - LaDier, Tovah (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Lamm, Donald S. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Lewin, Roger (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Levy-Leblond, Jean-Marc (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Lieberman, Bruce (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Loyd, Amy (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Luciano, Jeannie (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Lyon, Cecil (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - La (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - La (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Le (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - Le (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Li (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Lo (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Lu (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Ly (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - L Miscellaneous (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Machol, Robert E. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - Maienschein, Jane (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Maresca, Bruno (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Marsden, John (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Marshall, John D. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Masters, Judith (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Masuda, Yayoi (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Mayr, Ernst (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - McElroy, Michael B. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - McGowan, Alan (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - McShea, Dan (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Meier, Heinrich (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Mello, Felice (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Mendelsohn, Everett (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Mendelson, Robin (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Menzel, Kent E. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Merton, Robert K. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Milner, Richard (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Mirchandani, Ravi (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Moose, Bradley S. (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Ma (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Ma (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Ma (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Ma (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Ma (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Ma - Mb (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Mc (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Mc (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Mc (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Me (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Me (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Mi (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Mi - Ml (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Mo (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Mo (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Mu - My (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - M Miscellaneous (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Nevraumont, Peter N. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Newell, Norman D. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Norretranders, Tor (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Na (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Ne (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Ne (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Ni (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - No (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Nt - Ny (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - N Miscellaneous (Box 90, Folder 2)